{
    "id": "dc94577865db45f98877ea3b2ebdf972",
    "title": "Sentence Correction Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The old woman grew stronger ....................... began to move about.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e0f719f7b6c64bfead4747beafca070f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He had been walking for ..................... three miles.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "near",
                "nearly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aaa9d7b022f74d329e4660209ffd7b4e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do ....................... to our house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "came"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "040faee2552049ff9fa940b0a92a05fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "He returned last year and we .................. quite happy to see him again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bbecde1c5ffb4532b30ee788b4c3b69b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Here is a ..................... of wisdom.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "peace",
                "piece"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "68efcf844dc2416990d81e88f0f40fb9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ...................... a beautiful dress for you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "choosen",
                "chose",
                "chosen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6eb2bc51f9d443df84fd51b29a17c4a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ..................... an area where the harvest had failed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reached to",
                "reached",
                "reached at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "79e45962b9b14571be6f26dedf9ace48"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... a beautiful picture it is!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "122bd5936a964d7d8a4a512279f81b92"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ....................... his wife to look after their children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "told",
                "told to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "573e5fcfe28c4b869f2d2da53bcc05f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have so ...................... to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many work",
                "many works",
                "much work"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a87ada4f5c0f428287371a930dc1f1f7"
        }
    ]
}